{
    "subject": "resource/Diana_Gurtskaya",
    "predicate": "property/dateOfBirth",
    "object": "1978-07-02",
    "human_readable": "Diana Gurtskaya was born on July 2, 1978.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9216523766517639,
            "question": "When was Diana Gurtskaya born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8099396228790283,
            "question": "What is Diana Gurtskaya's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7826927900314331,
            "question": "What month and day was Diana Gurtskaya born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7579039931297302,
            "question": "July 2nd marks what significant event in Diana Gurtskaya's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6172824501991272,
            "question": "What is Diana Gurtskaya's age as of today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5025516152381897,
            "question": "Is Diana Gurtskaya a millennial?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4927481710910797,
            "question": "In what year did Diana Gurtskaya enter the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3593290448188782,
            "question": "If today is October 26th, how many days have passed since Diana Gurtskaya's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2135814130306244,
            "question": "What are some notable events that happened on July 2nd throughout history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05261695757508278,
            "question": "Does July fall in the summer season in most of the world?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Diana Gurtskaya was born on July 2, 1978.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1965_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some notable events that happened on July 2nd throughout history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1965_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If today is October 26th, how many days have passed since Diana Gurtskaya's birth?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1965_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Diana Gurtskaya enter the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1965_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1965_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1965_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1965_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1965_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1965_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1965_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1965_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1965_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1965_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1965_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}